Watch yourself.
Us is a horror, mystery film directed by Jordan Peele.
Husband and wife Gabe and Adelaide Wilson take their kids to their
beach house expecting to unplug and unwind with friends.
But as night descends, their serenity turns to tension and chaos
when some shocking visitors arrive uninvited.
Adelaide Wilson / Red, played by Lupita Nyong'o.
Gabe Wilson / Abraham, played by Winston Duke.
Kitty Tyler / Dahlia, played by Elisabeth Moss.
Josh Tyler / Tex, played by Tim Heidecker.
Zora Wilson / Umbrae, played by Shahadi Wright Joseph.
Jason Wilson / Pluto, played by Evan Alex.
Us is a 2019 American psychological horror film written and directed by Jordan Peele, and
starring Lupita Nyong'o, Winston Duke, Elisabeth Moss and Tim Heidecker.
The story follows Adelaide Wilson and her family, who are attacked by a
group of menacing doppelgängers, called the "Tethered".
The project was announced in February 2018.
Peele produced the film alongside Jason Blum and Sean McKittrick, having
previously collaborated with them on Get Out and BlacKkKlansman.
Filming took place in California, including Los Angeles,
Pasadena and Santa Cruz, from July to October 2018.
Us premiered at South by Southwest on March 8, 2019, and was theatrically
released in the United States on March 22, by Universal Pictures.
It received widespread critical acclaim, and grossed $256 million against
a budget of $20 million, making it a commercial success.
The film explores themes of mask, boardwalk,
murder, psychological thriller, fear.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.